<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><introduction>The episode opens at the Royal Candy Vault in the Candy Kingdom. It is night time. Two Banana Guards stand watch outside the dormitory.</introduction>
    <line><character>Right Guard</character><dialogue>I'm scared it'll come back tonight.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Left Guard</character><dialogue>Me too.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Right Guard</character><dialogue>Can we hold hands?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Left Guard</character><dialogue>I need my hand to hold my spear.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Right Guard</character><dialogue>Why don't you use your other hand?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Left Guard</character><dialogue>Oh, that's a good idea. <stage>He holds out his hand.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Right Guard</character><dialogue>But... I need this hand to hold my spear.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Left Guard</character><dialogue>Use your other one.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Right Guard</character><dialogue><stage>Tries to reach the other guard's left hand with his own left hand.</stage> Aw, it won't reach.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Left Guard</character><dialogue>Oh no.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Right Guard</character><dialogue>Wait! <stage>He turns around to face the wall so that they can hold each other's left hands.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Left Guard</character><dialogue>Oh-</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Both guards</character><dialogue><stage>Together</stage> Oh!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Left Guard</character><dialogue>Hooray.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Right Guard</character><dialogue><stage>Facing the wall</stage> This is less scary because now I won't see the monster coming.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>A growling is heard. The guard facing the wall hears it, but the guard on the left doesn't because he has been distracted by his own spear.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Left Guard</character><dialogue>Wow. You know, I just noticed these things have rings on the end. It must be for blowing bubbles. <stage>Twirls spear.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>They both scream as they are snatched away by the hand of a monster. There is a slurping sound and they go quiet. Brown ooze begins to seep towards the dormitory entrance, followed by the monster itself. It pushes the doors open, where there are many banana guards sleeping in bunks. It grabs one of them.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Banana Guard</character><dialogue>Huh? <stage>Screams</stage> It's back!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The monster hisses and spits ooze onto the guard's face, muffling him. He grabs another guard and does the same.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Banana Guard</character><dialogue>Huh?</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The monster grabs a third guard, but it shapeshifts and is revealed to be Jake the Dog in disguise.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Surprise! <stage>He bites the monster's hand and latches on.</stage> Finn, get in here! <stage>He and the monster continue fighting.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn sits up from one of the bunks. He is also in a banana guard disguise.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Hmm. Okay. Yeah! <stage>He draws his sword.</stage> Sic em, Jake! Ha! <stage>He jumps down from the bunk onto the monster's chest, where Jake has it pinned down.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Feeling good, buddy?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I'm good. But this chump's about to get slain!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Struggling to keep the monster's arms restrained.</stage> Slay him quick. He's got crazy devil strength!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>No prob. Here comes the slay...</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>As Finn looks into the monster's eyes, he hallucinates the face of Fern superimposed over it.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Fern face</character><dialogue>Don't kill me, Finn.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Um... Here I go! <stage>Unconvincing enthusiasm</stage> Mathematical!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Finn, are you doing the thing?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Fern face</character><dialogue>I'm your friend. I'm you.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Jake, maybe you should slay this guy?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Aw, dude, you are doing the thing again!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Fern face</character><dialogue>I'm you!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The sound of a weed whacker begins to grow in volume.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Slay him!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Suddenly, the scene cuts to a flashback. A time card reads "That morning." Finn and Princess Bubblegum are walking through the Candy Kingdom together, both wearing baseball kit.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Princess Bubblegum</character><dialogue>Thanks again for coming out to coach. The jamboree's always a big morale boost for the troops.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Yeah. It's, uh, a nice distraction.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Princess Bubblegum</character><dialogue>Hmm. So how are you holding up after all the Fern stuff?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>It's been a rough month, PB. I know Fern was an angry guy who tried to kill me, but I still feel awful about the way he went. It's really messing with me.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Princess Bubblegum</character><dialogue>Oh, Finn, I'm so sorry. Death is no laughing mat- <stage>She suddenly slips on an oversized banana peel and comedically falls to the ground. She examines the sticker on the banana peel.</stage> Banana guard number 216?! Oh my glob, he's dead! <stage>She sees more peels, covered in brown ooze.</stage> This is a banana fudge massacre!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>A group of banana guards approach them in a panic.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Banana Guards</character><dialogue><stage>Together</stage> Princess?! Princess?!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Princess Bubblegum</character><dialogue>Guys, what happened?!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Banana Guard</character><dialogue>A terrible monster kidnapped squadron five!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Another Banana Guard</character><dialogue>It looked like a banana, but it peeled other bananas!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>All</character><dialogue><stage>Together</stage> Traitor! Traitor! Traitor! Traitor! Traitor, traitor!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Princess Bubblegum</character><dialogue>A banana and fudge monster?! That's candy tech. Okay, who's behind this? <stage>She turns to Finn.</stage> Finn! I need you and Jake to guard the barracks tonight. If this creep comes back and lays a finger on my guards, you show no mercy.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Um... Yeah, I'll... do my best.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The flashback ends. Finn is still poised to strike down the monster. The buzzing of the weed whacker continues.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Finn! Finn, stop showing mercy!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The monster manages to break Jake's grip and frees its hands, then kicks Finn off its chest.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Oh, no! I dinked it!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The monster roars and shrieks at them, and then breaks through a wall and flees into the night. All the banana guards leap down from their bunks and begin running away in a panic. Jake is lying deflated on the ground.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Jake, I'm sorry! I- I couldn't do it!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Pained</stage> Love you forever, man, but your guilt's hurting the team dynamics.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I know. I'm gonna go make it right! <stage>He exits in pursuit of the monster.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Cool. I'm gonna make peace with my aging body.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn watches the monster run away into the night. He shakes himself and sets off in pursuit. He catches up, climbs onto the back of the monster's neck, and raises his sword.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>No mercy this time, banana boy! I don't care why you're doing this or if you have a... a tragic past. <stage>Fern's face appears again</stage> I don't care! I'm hard like that.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Fern face</character><dialogue>Don't kill me, Finn.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Growls</stage> Nope!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>He gives up, taking his sword away from the monster's neck. The monster notices him and screeches.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Oh, gross!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The monster headbutts him off its neck and into some nearby bushes.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>What the heck is my problem?!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The monster turns and spits fudge at him.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Aw, fudge!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>It seems like the fudge is going to hit Finn, but it is deflected by a mysterious projectile and lands on the monster's own face.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Huh?! How'd I do that?!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The monster retreats. Huntress Wizard suddenly appears next to Finn, hanging upside down from a tree.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>Um, it's getting away.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Aah! Oh, Huntress Wizard!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>Hey, Finn. <stage>She uses a magic arrow to create a vine in the direction of the monster.</stage> Come on! After that booger!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn climbs onto her back and Huntress Wizard hops onto the vine, going in pursuit of the monster again.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Thanks for the save, HW.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>Mm-hmm.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>You're chasing that grabby banana too, huh?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>I'm hunting it. It's an invasive species that's been destroying the local ecosystem with its nasty hot fudge. It's name is the Grumbo. It's a name that I made up just now... because you can't hunt what you can't name.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Yeah, makes sense.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>Hmm.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Small talking</stage> So how you been?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>Finn, I saw you falter back there. Why did you hesitate before you dealt the final blow?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Sighs</stage> It keeps happening since I aced Fern. Every time I'm about to wail on some monster, I remember seeing Fern go kaboom... and the guilt paralyzes me. I can't seem to final blow anybody.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>A flashback to Fern's death is shown while Finn talks.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>I see. Okay, let's vanquish your mental block. Because I'll need your help to defeat the Grumbo. It's a two-huntress job.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>The second huntress is me.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>Yes.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Huntress Wizard leaps down from the vine, startling a fat squirrel which is eating the fudge left behind by the Grumbo.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>The trail goes gold here. I mean, the fudge is still hot, but that squirrel dude just ate most of it.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Climbing off her back.</stage> What? No! Ugh, I should have struck when I had the chance! Or not struck Fern when I didn't have the chance? Ugh! I don't even know anymore.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>This is just me talking, but it sounds like Fern was already headed down a dark road. Sounds like he was a bad version of yourself that you had to destroy in order to become an even tighter version of yourself. Does that sounds about right?</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>They hear a distant whimpering and follow it to a cave.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>Looks like we got some hot fudge on our hands. Okay, let's review our roles. When I take out its legs, you strike the underbelly. Got it?</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Huntress Wizard manifests a javelin, and Finn draws his sword. They enter the cave.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I can do this. I'm 90% sure I can do this. Gonna slice right through that sweet Fern face.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>Shh!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The whimpering continues, and the Grumbo can be heard snoring. Finn and Huntress Wizard find it asleep, hanging from the roof of the cave.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>Ready?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Unconvincingly</stage> Yes.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Huntress hurls her javelin at the Grumbo, but it wakes up and dodges the attack. It drops to the floor to face its attackers.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>Duck - I guess.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Huh?</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Huntress Wizard avoids the Grumbo's headbutt, but Finn fails to react and is thrown across the room. Huntress runs up to the creature and kicks it in the chin.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>Bicycle kick!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>She manifests an arrow with rope and uses it to bind the Grumbo's legs together. It crashes to the floor.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>Now, Finn! Coop-degrassi!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Okay, time to final blow it!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>He leaps onto the Grumbo's neck with a battlecry and raises his sword. Once again, Fern's face appears.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Fern face</character><dialogue>Finn, don't you love me?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>To Huntress</stage> Uh, can we maybe switch roles?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue><stage>Struggling to keep the Grumbo bound</stage> Not again.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The Grumbo punches Finn away and catapults Huntress Wizard into a wall. The vines binding its legs discorporate.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Oops! Oops. Oops. Oops!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The Grumbo spits fudge at Finn. He leaps over the projectile and it sears his lower regions.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>High pitch voice</stage> HW, let's come back and try tomorrow!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue><stage>To herself</stage> Okay...</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>She throws another javelin at the Grumbo, distracting it from its attack against Finn. She stands T-posed, allowing it to charge at her.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Huntress Wizard, get out of the way!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Huntress Wizard remains where she is, watching the creature approach and doing nothing in response.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Think, think, think! <stage>Growls</stage> Okay, if I can't fix my mind, I gotta fool it. <stage>He points his sword at Huntress Wizard and thinks to himself.</stage> Attack. Attack. Attack.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Fern's face appears superimposed over Huntress Wizard's.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Fern face</character><dialogue>Finn, help me.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I'll save you, buddy.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn chases the monster and finally sinks his sword into its underbelly. It screeches and collapses, its huge body finally coming to rest just inches from Huntress Wizard's face. Fern pulls his sword from its belly with a grunt. The Grumbo's body bursts, covering Finn, Huntress, and the cave in banana goop. Finn's sword disintegrates from being covered in hot fudge.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I did it. Sorry I almost got you killed.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>It's cool. It's totally cool. I knew you just needed a push. That's why I very smartly pretended to throw myself in harm's way. <stage>She take's Finn's hand and helps him up.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>No, actually, that's not what did it.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>Yeah, right. We both know you're totally in love with me.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn smiles, and they kiss. When Finn opens his eyes, Fern is superimposed over Huntress Wizard's face again, and he gives a high pitched scream. A group of peeled banana guards emerge from another part of the cave, groaning.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Banana Guard</character><dialogue>Finn? Are you here to rescue us? Oh, glob! There's someone else here too!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Another Guard</character><dialogue>I don't have my peel! Don't look, don't look anyone! <stage>The banana guards continue indistinctly, embarrassed.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>It's okay, guys. Huntress Wizard is into natchy living.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Huntress Wizard</character><dialogue>Weird. These Grumbo remains are 100% artificial candy flesh - like straight out of a lab.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>I wonder who made him.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>A camera watches them from above. The scene changes to the ziggurat.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Mysterious character</character><dialogue>Who indeed? Who is the brilliant puppet master working tirelessly behind the scenes, completely unfazed by this minor, minor setback? <stage>He crosses out a picture of the Grumbo.</stage> Why, it's me - Uncle G. Ready yourself, Princezzin! Your boy hero will be no match for my next creation.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>An unknown monster is seen twitching in a tank.</stage></line>
    <credits>Episode ends</credits></xml>
