<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<xml><introduction>The episode opens in the Tree House. Finn is eating cereal and Jake is sipping coffee.</introduction>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Takes a spoonful of cereal and munches twice.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Slurps</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Huh?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I was just sipping my coffee.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Oh. <stage>Takes a spoonful of cereal and munches twice.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Slurps</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Munching</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Slurp</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Munching</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Slurp</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Both of them notice the pattern and begin repeating it rhythmically. On the third repeat, Finn only munches his cereal once, tricking Jake into sipping early and breaking the pattern. They both laugh. BMO joins them.</stage></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>I am also excited about today.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Oh, yeah?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Today is the first day of my new job.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>What's your new job, BMO?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Yeah, are you a spy? You know, 'cause of the overcoat?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>I'm a door-to-door salesman.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn and Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Together</stage> Oh.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>What are you selling?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>I've got so many great things. Like for the man about town, this piece of lint.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>I'll take it! <stage>He takes the lint.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Hooray, my first sale! That'll be four doubloons.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Can I pay you later?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Mm, the customer is always right!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Good attitude, BMO.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Well, gentlemen... got to chop that wood.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>BMO stands up clumsily, revealing that someone else is inside the overcoat and BMO is sitting on their head, pretending they are his own body. "BMO" almost knocks a glass off the table, but Finn catches it. He notices Ice King's robes and feet sticking out the bottom of the overcoat.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Whispering to Jake</stage> It's Ice King.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Whispering back</stage> I know.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Ice King</character><dialogue><stage>Peeks his face out the front of the overcoat and spots that Finn and Jake have seen him.</stage> Oh! <stage>He quickly closes the overcoat.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue><stage>Exiting</stage> Okay, wish me luck, fellas, even though I don't need-</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Ice King falls down the ladder, interrupting BMO. They both scream as they fall. There is a thud. Finn and Jake giggle at their shenanigans.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn and Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Together</stage> Aww.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>BMO and Ice King leave the Tree House.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Ice King</character><dialogue>Boy, this is great, huh? You and me out in the fresh air? Now, the key to being a tip-top salesman is to get the ol' foot in the door.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Bodies don't talk, Ice King.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Ice King</character><dialogue>Well, mine does.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Okay, then. If I say "My feet hurt," you can go "Woof woof." That's my dogs barking.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Ice King</character><dialogue>BMO, I think we're gonna make an unbeatable team.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Yeah, yeah! Let's go! Let's go! Let's go! Let's go! <stage>Kicking the sides of Ice King's head and laughing.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>A sword logo flies onto screen reading "Potential customer time!" The scene changes to Tree Trunks' house.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Tree Trunks</character><stage>Reading as she types on a typewriter</stage> "Chapter 3<dialogue>No Time For Sleeping. Elizabeth's heart was racing like a water mill after spring thaw. She knew her enemies were coming for her, but when? Suddenly, there was a knock at the door."</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Suddenly, there is a knock at the door.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Tree Trunks</character><dialogue>Oh! Oh. Oh, my goodness. Someone's at the door. That's all. <stage>She opens the door, finding BMO and Ice King.</stage> Hello.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Tree Trunks, how are your children? Can you believe this weather? <stage>After some fumbling, Ice King tips BMO's hat politely.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Tree Trunks</character><dialogue>So polite. Please, please come in.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue><stage>Taking a seat</stage> You have a lovely home.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Tree Trunks</character><dialogue>Here, have some apple pie.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Oh, thank you.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Ice King snatches the apple pie and takes it inside the overcoat.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Tree Trunks</character><dialogue>Now what can I do for you?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Oh, well, I'd like to show you what I'm selling today.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>He grunts and kicks Ice King, who is busy eating the pie inside the coat. Ice King puts his arms back into the sleeves and rummages through his and BMO's bag.</stage></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Okay, we have a broken branch, a half-eaten sandwich - oh, another ball of lint.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Tree Trunks</character><dialogue>Another?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>These are selling like red hots. A dust bunny - That's like a cage-free ball of lint. A doll's head, and a little velvet bag, tied tight at the top.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>While BMO is presenting the items, Ice King struggles to eat more of the apple pie with his tongue.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Tree Trunks</character><dialogue>I'll take the branch. My loose cash is up there in the flower jar. Help yourself.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Ice King makes his way to the shelf with the jar, stubbing his toe and smashing several plates on the way. He reaches into the jar and pulls out a huge roll of banknotes.</stage></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue><stage>Laughs happily as Ice King tosses the money wad from hand to hand. Tree Trunks joins the laughter, not really paying attention as she has been distracted by the branch.</stage> You have a lovely home! <stage>Ice King falls out the door and they both scream as they exit.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Mr. Pig</character><dialogue><stage>Entering</stage> What'd you buy, honey bunch?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Tree Trunks</character><dialogue>A branch.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Mr. Pig</character><dialogue>Huh. <stage>Tree Trunks turns him around and starts scratching his back with the branch.</stage> Huh? Oh. Ah, Tree Trunks, you're a financial genius.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue><stage>Laughing as he and Ice King leave the orchard.</stage> I can't believe we unloaded that branch. It wasn't even our best one. Oh, my. Shield my eyes from the sun.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Ice King</character><dialogue>Why?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Because I think I see our next customer. <stage>They watch a large chipmunk carrying a couple of acorns.</stage> Those nuts could be ours. Excuse me, little boy!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The chipmunk begins running, and Ice King begins chasing.</stage></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>How are your children?! Ice King, duck. Jump. Right. Right again. <stage>Laughs</stage> Left. Jump, jump. Left. Right. Left. Ice King, you're doing so good. You have not bumped into anything.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>They come to a stop.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Ice King</character><dialogue>BMO, where's the customer?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Oh, no. I was so excited about you not bumping into anything, I lost the customer. Ice King, I think we are lost.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>An animal howls. The scene fades to later. BMO and Ice King have arrived at a ziggurat.</stage></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Look. A house.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Ice King</character><dialogue>All I see is the inside of this coat.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>They approach a door.</stage></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>And... stop. Knock politely.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Ice King knocks, and footsteps are heard inside. A mysterious figure answers the door and beckons them inside.</stage></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Mysterious sentinel, you have a lovely home. <stage>Whispering to Ice King</stage> Turn. <stage>Continues talking to the mysterious figure</stage> How are your children? <stage>BMO gasps, noticing that the figure has disappeared.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Ice King wanders further into the zigurrat, where he finds Uncle Gumbald mixing liquids in a pair of test tubes.</stage></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Hello.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>One of the tubes produces a skull-shaped puff of smoke which floats towards BMO and Ice King. Gumbald retrieves an axe from beneath his desk.</stage></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>I'm a door-to-door salesman, ma'am.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The smoke enters the coat and Ice King is heard choking.</stage></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue><stage>Chuckling</stage> Oh, excuse my indigestion. <stage>He kicks Ice King.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Ice King</character><dialogue>Ouch.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>I have some wonderful new products, like, uh, this ball of lint. No, wait, this is the dust bunny. Uh... Oh, oh! I know - this velvet bag.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Gumbald raises the axe menacingly.</stage></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Did I mention that it contains Finn's teeth?</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Gumbald drops the axe to the ground and suddenly adopts a polite manner.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Gumbald</character><dialogue>Please, let's go in the parlor, where we can be more comfortable.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The scene changes. BMO, Ice King, and Gumbald are sat in the parlor while Gumbald examines the teeth.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Gumbald</character><dialogue>And you're sure these are Finn's teeth?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Yes.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Gumbald</character><dialogue>The same Finn who serves Princess Bubblegum, obstructs my plans, and plagues my thoughts?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Yes.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Gumbald</character><dialogue>Finn the Human's teeth?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>That's a BMO guarantee.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Ice King</character><dialogue><stage>Whispering</stage> Psst! Does Finn know you have his teeth? Because I don't think-</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue><stage>Interrupting</stage> Hey! I'm trying to close a sale here.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Gumbald</character><dialogue>I hope you accept silver. I can pay you immediately. <stage>Admiring the teeth</stage> Yes, my pretties.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The scene changes back to the Tree House. It is night.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Poor little guy. Still wearing out the shoe leather trying to make just one more lousy sale before coming home.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>He'll feel better after we have a little party for him.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn and Jake have prepared an "employee of the month" poster for BMO, and set out some cupcakes on the table.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Still, it's tough seeing your kid get his heart set on doing something he really sucks at.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>The door is heard. BMO and Ice King enter.</stage></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Hello, boys. Meet the salesman of the year. Or maybe of the decade. The Chinese food is on me. I mean, check out the loot. <stage>Ice King hands Finn a silver goblet.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Whispering to Jake</stage> It's real.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>What the heck did you sell to get this silver goblet?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Just a line of smooth talk and pipe dreams. Oh, and a set of human baby teeth.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Where did you even get a set of human baby teeth? <stage>Suddenly realizing</stage> Human baby teeth!! <stage>He rushes up to the bedroom and retrieves a box from a drawer. It's empty.</stage> BMO!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Branches and lint are moving like cray, Jake.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Finn shows BMO the empty box accusatively.</stage></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Oh, sure, I sold your baby teeth. I could sell any part of you.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>These were, like, the only things I had left from when I was a little kid.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Hey, you know what? We'll just go buy back those little pearly whites. I'm sure whoever bought them is like, "Why did I buy these things?" What possible use could some guy have for a set of human baby teeth? Unless he's an evil sorcerer or a mad scientist... He wasn't a mad scientist, was he?</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Well...</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>There is a pounding on the door. A load of Baby Teeth Finns break down the door and enter the Tree Fort.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>High pitch shriek</stage> Stay back, baby Finns. <stage>Babies begin climbing him, and he and Jake both scream.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue><stage>Groans nervously</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>A baby starts gnawing on Finn's arm. He punts it with his fist and it shatters a window as it flies through.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>They're made out of some kind of hard tooth-like material. Ouch. Ouch! Ice King, freeze these nightmare babies.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Ice King</character><dialogue>I'm not allowed to wear my crown. It's against BMO's dress code.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Just don't let them climb into your mouth!</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>A baby tries to enter Finn's mouth.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Hey, there, bitey boys. Get off of there. <stage>More babies attack Jake.</stage> Where's your baby manners? Eek.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Hmm. Maybe I sold too well.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Ice King</character><dialogue>Hey, you're a great salesman. Evil babies are not a problem for you. They're an opportunity.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Yeah. Where did I put those - Oh, here they are. <stage>Ice King pulls out a couple of sledgehammers.</stage> Gentlemen, could I interest you in a couple of sledgehammers? Perfect for smashing through minerals or composites.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue><stage>Being gnawed by babies</stage> I'll take one.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue>Me too!</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Great decision.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Ice King hands the hammers to Finn and Jake. Finn taps one of the babies and it disintegrates with a poof. He smashes a few more babies.</stage></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>A little tap is all it takes.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Jake</character><dialogue><stage>Smashing babies</stage> These baby-smashing hammers are great.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>They continue smashing all the babies. Gumbald is seen outside, watching through a telescope. After all the babies are smashed, Finn, Jake, and BMO begin sweeping up the mess.</stage></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>I'm sorry I caused such a mess. It's very bad for business.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Ice King</character><dialogue>Well, time to call it a day. <stage>He pulls out a clocking-in machine and a punchcard, and clocks out, then places a small hat atop his crown.</stage> The ice man leaveth.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>BMO</character><dialogue>Hey, wait. See you tomorrow, partner. <stage>They shake hands.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Ice King</character><dialogue>Until tomorrow.</dialogue></line>
    <line><character>Finn</character><dialogue>Yeah, you're not doing this tomorrow.</dialogue></line>
    <line><stage>Ice King exits, whistling. Gumbald watches through his telescope.</stage></line>
    <line><character>Gumbald</character><dialogue>Hmm. In retrospect, the attack would have worked much better were they not baby teeth. <stage>Clears throat.</stage></dialogue></line>
    <credits>Episode ends</credits></xml>
